good afternoon good afternoon you are from russia i am
добрый день добрый день вы из россии я
from ukraine they say khmelnitsk you are
из украины говорят хмельницке вы
enemies of dubna cruel this area what is the
врагов дубна жестокой эта область какая
speed of moscow when i accidentally
московская скорость когда я случайно вам
got you ukraine specially
попала ли вы украину специально
choose d set
выбираете д поставил
you want sucre intimate wait
вы хотите сукре интимный погоди на самом
actually we can do anything but
деле можем на любые но
you not what brought you  it’s shuklin
вас не вас что привело именно шуклин
yourself to talk about what you want to
сами поговорить что вы хотите о чем
talk about Ukrainians
поговорить украинцами
life and life let’s talk about life
жизни а жизнь давайте поговорим о жизни
yes let’s
да давайте
ask regular life how
спрашивайте штатной жизни ну как
in general what are the plans here it is life
вообще какие планы вот она жизнь
further plan and such that we must first
дальнейший план и такие что надо сначала
drive out of ukraine and equip
прогнать из украины и обустраивать
further
дальше
life just
жизнь просто просто
let’s keep on
давайте дальше
giving  even
давать еще
bitterer tears came from the waters from the
горше слез с есть пришли вод с
territory of the russian federation
территории российской федерации
invaders
оккупанты
invaders to help the Donetsk shop of
оккупанты помочь донецкую лавку
Donetsk cattle ukraine and rashists came to
донецкого скота украина и рашисты пришли
help us get rid of us interesting
помочь нам избавиться от нас интересно
it’s
это
not so tell
не так расскажите
[music]
[музыка]
how they infringed on the packing yes no
как ущемляли получается укладку да нет
how
как
they did not agree with the choice of
они не согласились с выбором
maidan the president let’s  let's start let's start
майдану президент давайте давайте начнет
almost by dates  you can sort it out,
давайте по датам почти начнем разбирать
you can name it yes, well, no, but that’s
можете назвать да ну так нет а вот
exactly who exactly what body,
именно так кто конкретно какой орган так
so for example, how didn’t agree on what
вот например как не согласился в какой
day so that you understand where we are from the beach,
день чтобы вы поняли откуда мы пляже
look when the pastor asks for a maidan so
посмотрите когда пастор прошу майдан так
in
в
[music]
[музыка]
Donetsk Lugansk people agreed people
донецке луганске люди согласились людей
people this specifically  who are all absolutely
люди это конкретно кто все абсолютно
people or how they showed that the
люди или как как они показали что
majority
большинство
is how many 70 percent 80 how did you find out
то сколько 70 процентов 80 как вы узнали
how you got the information that this
откуда у вас информация что это
majority was
большинство было
because they were against the
потому что они были против
rally
митинга
to come
приехать
[music]
[музыка]
from the cake, let's say that, it turns out that there
из торта давайте так то есть получается
were rallies there in Donetsk  at the same time,
митинги там донецке были в этом при этом
5000 people rally here for millions of
5000 человек митинг вот на миллионы
units, for example, and thousands of people, this is the
единиц например и тысяч людей это
majority
большинство
yes no of course no right yes, that is,
да нет конечно нет правильно да то есть
you had rallies in russia there are rallies in
были митинги у вас в россии есть митинги
china there were
китае есть были
good so how did the war start
хорошо так с чего началась война
well tell me
ну расскажите мне
war war
война война
how do you say what is there  we are something very
как вы скажете что там мы что-то очень
for
для
whom
кого
what kind of war let's remove the bathhouse for now
какая война давайте пока уберем баню вот
it looks like they infringed on someone specific
выглядит ущемляли кого конкретный как
how and when they started to infringe  Can you
как и когда начали ущемлять можете
bring examples
примеры довести
after the Maidan as a note, look, we
после майдана как нотка посмотрите мы
just decided that your eyes were
только что решили что глаза у вас
forbidden, it is hello, officially the
запретили она здравствуй официально
Russian language
русский язык
level, the Ukrainian language was
уровне украинский язык был
because because it
потому что потому что
makes you spirit in Ukrainian it
заставляет духом на украинском так и
was yes yes, we have the state language
было да да у нас государственный язык
Ukrainian
украинский
you live you live in  the Moscow region
вы живете вы живете в московской области
so you come when, for example, to the
так вы приходите когда например в
hospital or to the police,
больницу так или в полицию вызову
fill out the forms in Chechen in
заполняйте на чеченском бланки на
Buryat or Russian, I’m
бурятском или на русском я
true, yes, although you have a whole
правда да хотя у вас есть целый
republic, so on, why is a
республики так дальше так то почему
Ukrainian if you have state
украинец если у вас государственные
downloads of these
загрузки этих
republics, the language is considered a second language and
республик язык считается вторым языком и
it works almost again let's
он действует почти еще раз давайте
go so you come here you have
давайте так вы приходите у вас вот
russia there is russia there is a state
россия есть россия есть государство
ukraine russia a federal ukraine a
украина россия федеративная украина
unitary state so in ukraine the
унитарное государство так в украине
state language is ukrainian it is logical
государственный язык украинский логично
that we have all the documents are in
что у нас все документы идут на
ukrainian and in your constitution it will say
украинском а у вас в конституции скажет
that you have a state language  Russian
что у вас государственный язык русский
which is a lot of language - the price of communication  it’s
который язык много- цена общение
your multinational people and
многонационального вашего народа и
that’s why when you come to state
поэтому вы приходя в государственные
institutions you fill in in Russian
учреждения вы заполняете на русском
true yes yes, why, for example, they
правда да да то почему например они на
come to a Chechen a Chechen in Moscow, then
чеченца вот приходит чеченец в москве то
I want in Chechen don’t give a form no
я хочу на чеченском не дайте бланк нет
such truth there is no such thing for 8 donut
такого правда нет такого за 8 пончик
otherwise he writes in Polish
иначе приходит на польском пишет
what is the problem
в чем проблема
because I don’t know the problems of the problems, it was
потому что я не знаю проблем проблем
just the Russian language, but before that,
просто русский язык был но грей до этого
inside the gland, we have the
потом внутри железы у нас
state language in the constitution, the
государственный язык в конституции
Ukrainian Ukrainian language is enshrined in
украинский украинский язык закреплен у
our country and what it has always been like, well, the duty
нас и в чем он всегда был так ну долга
to Russian was the praetor, the language was not the
на русский был претора языком не был
second  we didn’t have a language 2 it’s not the
вторым языком не было у нас 2 не
youth of the second language
молодость второго языка
show in which document in the constitution
покажите в каком документе в конституции
where it says that we have a
где у нас написано что у нас там есть
second state language there
второй государственный язык
well somehow lives with the Russian language
ну как-то живет с русским языком до
Russian
выйдешь да есть люди которые по русски
grit and
грит и
problems, why did they start how to clean it up
проблем зачем начали как бы его убирать
again in general, what do you see, we have the
вообще еще раз какой смотрите у нас есть
state language Ukrainian so  didn’t
государственный язык украинский так не
rest at least a little
отдыхал хоть немного у
you have people who speak
вас есть люди которые говорят на
Chechen
чеченском
no one forces it doesn’t burn and
никто не заставляет не горит и у нас
no one forces us to speak
никто не заставляет говорить на
Chechen or Russian speak the seeds
чеченском или на русском говори семена
as you like, well, for example, state
как хочешь ну например государственные
institutions,
учреждения
they, as authorities, they
они как органы власти они свои дела
conduct their production affairs in Russian watch the
производства ведут на русском смотреть
video  even in u-tube when they give
видео даже в ю-тубе когда они дают
humanitarian aid because they say
гуманитарную помощь потому что говорят
speak Ukrainian where where they don’t give
говорите на украинском где где не дают
mental help it was
ментально помощь был
officially there that a person was
официально есть это что там человеку там
refused there he came for example to the hospital
отказали он пришел например в больницу
he was told we won’t treat you
ему сказали не мы тебя не полечим потому
because you speak Russian  yes, no,
что ты говоришь по-русски есть нет
well, even the doctors speak Russian by me and they speak Russian a
ну даже врачи мной и говорят по-русски
dream and it’s normal now and now Russia is
мечту и нормально сейчас и сейчас россия
bombing Odessa near Russian-speaking Kharkiv
бомбит у русскоязычных харьков одессу
there is a sky that most of its row is
там небо который большинство его ряд
Russian yes they calmly say Rus
русски да они спокойно говорят руси
no one is forcing them people now
никто их не заставлять люди сейчас
in Russian
по-русски
Russian people there are not Russian Russian
русские люди там не русские
-speaking
русскоязычные
do not confuse Russian and Russian speakers,
не путайте русских и русскоязычных
for example, if now the Buryats
например если если сейчас буряты
begin to speak Russian, they
начинают говорить по-русски они стают
become Russian
этого русскими
even like Ukrainians who come
даже как люди украинцы которые приезжают
to the city and start speaking Russian
в город и начинает говорить по-русски
because they spoke Russian in the city,
потому что в городе говорили по-русски
plus of use, they don’t get tired of this as
то плюс of use они же не устают от этого
Russians,
русскими
let's get back
давайте вернемся так
here, let's get back to him and about the
уж его сюда давайте вернемся ним и про
language now what  how and who when it started to
язык теперь что как и кто когда начал
infringe specifically here
ущемлять конкретно вот
in the Donbass there is a war going on really let's
на донбассе идет война правда давайте
start it became worth why your food is
начнем стал стоит зачем вашу еду
contentment let's why tell me the
довольство давайте зачем назовите мне
date when the troops went there
дату когда пошли туда войска
were let's spend it looking for well
были давайте его трачу искать хорошо
seeing off
проводя
I'll tell you when the troops went to ukraine
я вам скажу когда пошли войска в украину
bella current now what let's  so
белла тока сейчас какая давайте так
let's while you are looking, I'll tell you
давайте пока вы ищете я вам скажу
on March 26 there was a seizure of Crimea, the Russian invasion of
26 марта был захват крыма вторжение
this and on the territory of the
российской этого а на территории
Donetsk region it is Dutch on
донецкой области это голландская 12
April 12, 2014,
апреля 2014 года
Russian terrorists led by
террористы российский во главе с гиркин
Girkin crossed the border and captured the city of
нам перешли границу и захватили город
Slavyansk
славянск и
and two days later the
через два дня началась
anti-terrorist operation began on April 14
антитеррористическая операция 14 апреля
[  music] to
[музыка]
be
быть
around
всему
April 7th it turns out that on April 7th which
7 апреля получается что 7 апреля какой
document show started on 7th a  tell me about the
документ покажите началось 7 апреля то о
reasons,
причинах
show a document, some kind of document,
покажите документ какой то есть документ
on April 12, before
12 апреля до
the CIS, the
собралась снг
National Security and Defense Council met
совет национальной безопасности и
after the capture of Slavyansk and announced
после захвата славянска и огласил
ata-ata for an hour, officially substitution 14
ата-ата на час официально подмена 14
[music]
[музыка]
and
и
here there is a document you are looking
вот конкретно есть документ вы смотрите
at,
я сейчас
I’ll cover it now,
я сейчас прикрою
okay, in short  less .  when, but
ладно короче менее . когда но
not in this, the meaning was shell-shocked in the fact that no
не в этом смысл контузил в том что как
matter why you don’t watch how we started
бы зачем вы не смотрите как мы начали
watching again, I will choose the chronology
смотреть еще раз я выберу хронологию
on April 12, 2000 it’s even difficult for God to submit
12-го апреля 2000 даже трудно подачи
which document I have a document
бога какой документ у меня есть документ
at 12 April 12 it was customary
в 12 12 апреля было принято
to watch April 12 Russian  the terrorist
смотреть 12 апреля российский террорист
Girkin captured the city of Slavyansk so they entered the
гиркин захватил город славянск так вошли
armed captured the police there a hut
вооруженного захватили полицию там избу
and so on the
и так дальше
Russian hole from see who
российский дыра из смотрите кто игорь
Igor Strelkov-Girkin is a citizen of what he is in the FSB of
стрелков-гиркин гражданин он какой в фсб
Russia and everything is not a Ukrainian further
россии да все не украинец на дальше
captured the city in Ukraine and after
захватил город в украине так и после
this capture the light of
этого захвата собралась свет
national security gathered and  defense and
национального безопасности и обороны и
decided to start an
приняла решение про начала
anti-terrorist operation that
антитеррористической операции которая
began on April 14 and look again
началась 14 апреля и смотрите еще раз
On April 12, Russian militants entered a
12 апреля российские боевики зашли в
Ukrainian city and captured this is how
украинский город и захватили вот как как
you think if I gathered 50 people
вы считаете если бы я собрал 50 человек
and
и
captured Bryansk
захватил брянск
when again if I gather 50 people
когда еще раз если я собираю 50 человек
and capture  police station
и захватываю отделение полиции
armed grenade launcher police in
вооруженных гранатомета полиции в
Bryansk I will be terrorists
брянске я буду террористам
germin was also
гермин тоже был
in April,
в апреле
once again, it means after they were
еще раз значит после они были
terrorists they entered the territory of a
террористами нас они вошли на территорию
foreign state,
чужого государства
look, they will still get to
смотри они будут добралась еще
consider, let's do it if in Bryansk
рассмотреть давайте так если в брянске
some people spend there an apple party there for
какие-то там проводят там партия яблоко
a conditional moment, so something does
условный какой-то миг так что то не
n’t agree with something and  i gather 50
чем-то не согласны и я собираю 50
people and we come with grenade launchers with
человек и мы приходим с гранатометами с
machine guns we seize the police station
автоматами захватываем отделение полиции
in bryansk
в брянске
let's go further they were a friend they
давайте дальше они другом было они
came as volunteers wait I also
пришли добровольцами подождите я тоже
voluntarily here I voluntarily came to
добровольно вот я добровольно пришел в
bryansk voluntarily you came brass
брянске добровольно вы пришли brass
when when you passed tanks behind
когда когда вы за брянске прошли танки
bryansk look at what they are  let’s go
на предмет смотри какие они пошли
inserting no Slavic tanks
вставив никаких танков славянске не было
before these parts, we are clear on the facts, let’s go
до эти части мы четко по фактам давайте
according to my husband’s documents, I don’t know something,
по документам у мужа я что-то не знаю
maybe I live in Ukraine, I missed something,
может я вот живу в украине что-то
maybe I don’t know, I went somewhere this week, maybe I
может я в эту неделю где-то не знаю уход
missed  this leg,
может и пропустил эту ногу
let me wonder,
давайте мне интересно
for some reason, all Russians are trying here
я почему-то все русские пробуют вот
trying for hours now I will find it now and
пробует часа сейчас я найду вот сейчас и
we can’t find the cheat
чит не находим
[music]
[музыка]
if you say h  then they came there
если вы говорите что они пришли там
tables who called them,
таблиц кто их призвал
someone these specific people, like
кто-то этих какие конкретно людям как
people, for example, maybe some dude
люди например может меня какой-то чувак
from Bryansk, just a man, can take me and call and
с брянска просто мужик взять и позвать и
come here with the troops, maybe I
приди сюда с войсками можно меня не
can’t, this release will also be like this if the
может это релиз тоже будем как это если
official authorities here  for example, that is, a
официальной власти вот например то есть
movie of you and it would not be so someone who
кино вас и это не было бы так кто то кто
then had a quota was the regional council of
тогда было квоты был областной совет
Donetsk the Donetsk regional council did
донецкий областной совет никаких
not call for any terrorists
террористов не призывал
, but terrorists look at the person
пути но террористы смотри человек
who comes
который приходит
theoretically oh so let's find
теоретически ах ты так давайте находим
if I come with a weapon and collect a letter with a
если я приду с оружием и письму соберу
detachment  I’ll come as a serviceman I’ll
отряд приду служивым захвачу отделение
capture the police station in Bryansk, for example, the glyph of Kursk,
полиции в брянске например глиф курске
who will I be
кем я буду
absolutely the base if Girkin came here with an
абсолютно базе если гиркин пришел сюда с
armed detachment, he’s thorny
вооруженным отрядом захвате он тернист
at the wrong time when everything was fine with you
не в то время когда у вас все было
and so
хорошо и чтобы
that everything was calm like rallies
все спокойно было типа митинги какие-то
, we always had rallies  and in Russia, which one
были у нас всегда митинги и в россии
may have
может
ended, well, tell me,
закончилась какая конкретно ну скажите
let's
давайте
look at the illegal overthrow in short,
смотрите незаконное короче свержение
let's look for laws not to set and
давайте подыщите законы не задавать и
so what,
так какая же что
let’s say who invited them if they are not
скажем кто пригласил их если они не
terrorists who what
террористы кто какой орган власть
local authority can at least who called them yes
местный может хотя бы кто их призвал да
I don’t know I’ll say look they’re right
я не знаю я скажу смотрите они прям у
they never had anyone there was no project it
них никогда не было никого не был проект
didn’t
не было
turn out that a
получается что
person
человек
just don’t look at
просто не смотри на
look, we are talking about where to start recording,
смотрите мы говорим с чего начать запись
and two days later the throat was also captured by
а через два дня была захвачена горловка
militant detachments
также отрядами боевиков
there, by the way, in the throat, they
там кстати в горловке дать через два дня
killed a deputy of the local
убили депутата местного совета
council, if we are talking about victims,
вот если мы говорим про жертвы так вот и
then they started killing people, that is, if
тогда начали убивать людей то есть если
he was in the throat, he  the representative is a
он в горловке был он представитель
resident of the Donbass, a deputy and we didn’t
житель донбасса депутат и мы не
like that the militants
понравилось что боевики
because of Girkin oh you started giving
из-за гиркин ой вы начали дал еще раз
me again no no no we’ll figure it out
меня нет нет нет еще разберемся
in the city they’ll kill you and you came militants and the
в городе убьют и вы пришли боевики и
Russians
российские
took off the Ukrainian flag a man a deputy of the
сняли украинский флаг человек депутат
city council hung the
городского совета по вешал назад
Ukrainian flag back to him for this  ripped
украинский флаг ему за это вспороли
open his stomach killed him
живот убили его
take grab throat
возьмите возьмите захват горловки
write write
напишите пишу
vladimir fisherman yuri correction google
владимир рыбак юрий поправка загуглите
murder
убийство
fisherman
рыбак
thief
воровка
enter  the murder of vladimir the fisherman
введите убийство владимира рыбака
[music] by
[музыка]
separatists after hours it would be so ebay 17
сепаратистами после часов бы так ebay 17
mass attempt to own the flag of the dnr youtube to the
масса попытку свой флаг днр ютюба
rhine walls militants or were carried out by the
рейнским стенам боевики или велись
fisherman
рыбака
[music]
[музыка]
let's lie down like this you just
давайте так полежите вот вы только что
read it means look militants have come
прочитали значит смотрите пришли боевики
seized the throat the legally elected
захватили горловку законно избранный
deputy returned the Ukrainian flag for this
депутат вернул флаг украинский за это
he was killed in this way, that is, it turns out that the terrorists came to
его убили так то есть получается пришли
everyone who
террористы всех кто
was for Ukraine, they began to kill, they began to
был за украину начали убивать они начали
run away there, he’s not only one of this, the
убегать там он же не только одним этого
first ones started before that, you can
первые начали же до этого можете назвать
name some victims who were killed by Ukraine,
вот какие то жертвы кого убивала украина
for example, of course, in Odessa, to complicate,
например конечно в одессе к усложнению
let’s do it if he surrenders too  On May 2,
давайте так если отдастся тоже 2 мая
let's now analyze Slavyansk,
давайте могут сейчас разбираем славянск
so from March 12 to April 12, name
так вот 12 марта по 12 апреля назовите
if there is something Ukraine brought someone with tanks who
если там что-то украина танками кого-то
tell me who the deceased
довела кто назовите мне кто погибший
is until April 12 before the
есть до 12 апреля до начала
invasion, this is in the Donbass,
вторжения вот это в донбасс
well, I gave you an example, you checked
ну вот я вам назвал пример вы проверили
then a deputy of the City Council was killed, another
тогда был убит депутат горсовета еще
militant
боевик
turns out we see that Russia did not
получается мы смотрим что россия не
come  to beat Ukrainian
пришли начали захватывать украинские
cities like this and kill Ukrainian citizens
города так и убивать украинских граждан
who stood for Ukraine and absurdity I
которые выступали за украину и абсурд я
once again who Igor Girkin is
еще раз кто такой игорь гиркин
[music]
[музыка]
let's say this is not a Ukrainian really
давайте так это это не украинец правда
no, that is, not Ukrainians yes if an Arab
нет то есть не украинцы да если араб
let's analyze let's take it according to the
давайте давайте разберем давайте по
legislation of the Russian Federation
законодательству российской федерации
so
так
his actions  this participation in illegal
его действия это участие в незаконных
armed groups is true
вооруженных формированиях правда
why he has not yet been convicted in Russia
почему он до сих пор не осужден в россии
for this
за это
why in Russia a terrorist who
почему в россии террорист который
captured cities in a foreign country in such a way
захватывал в чужой стране города так
conducted illegal hostilities is not
вёл незаконные боевые действия не
prosecuted in Russia and he is there
преследуется в россии причем он там
why you probably because no one was
вот вы наверно потому что никого не
convicted
осудили
let's  so if he
давайте так если он так
participated in illegal armed
участвовал в незаконных вооруженных
groups so we just
формированиях так мы мы только что
figured out that it wasn’t ukraine that started
разобрали что не украина начала
laws and laws were going on in the yard so you
законы и законы шел на дворе так ты
again are not law and power if this is a
опять не закон и власть если это
legal formation so what
законные формирование так какой страны
country were these laws of war me wait for the general
это были законы войны меня подожди общей
legal any person any  a person
законны любой человек любой человек
just comes and helps, but this is not the
просто приходит и помогает но это не
law, see  let's have the
закон смотрите давайте так вот есть
armed forces of ukraine for example
вооруженные силы украины например
filled power
заполнил власть
not ukrainian and russian what
не украинский и российский каким
armed forces he belonged to when he
вооруженным силам он относился когда
came
пришел
[music]
[музыка]
such laws let's say who the militias of
такое законы давайте так кто ополченцы
donbass that such a state did not
донбасса что такое государство не
elegantly represent any other
элегантно никакого того другого
state
государства
they took two so in Donetsk there was a Donetsk
они взяли два так в донецке был донецкий
regional  advice
областной совет
here is the party of the region, a deputy from the
вот там партия региона депутата из
party of regions, and not the legally elected
партии регионов а не законно избранные
, the
были
elected were chained, yes, they called for, they
закованы избранные да они призывали они
created some kind of armed
создавали какие-то вооруженные
formations, they didn’t create the
формирования не создавали
question, yes, you’re right to start and thoughts,
вопрос да вы правильно начинать и мысли
and who created
а кто создавал
who
кто
you start selling and who created your own
вы начинать продавать и кто создал свой
Ukraine did not create Donetsk  the area
украина не создавала донецкая область
where they created who created
где создавала кто создал
who created whom the formation of who who
кто создал кого формирование кто кто
recruited these militias who
набирал вот этих ополченцев кто
people
люди
disagree
не согласен
carbon who represented these people
углерод кто представлял этих людей
some kind of president of the premiere action movie then
какой-то президентом премьеры боевик то
people don’t like the islands create you
люди как не любят острова творите вы
understand that you already got so who to
поняли что вы уже попали так кто
whom from the currency let’s do it  if a
кому от валютным давайте так если
person comes  am conditionally the militia,
человек приходит там условно ополчение
then who gives him weapons
то кто ему выдает оружие
, a surname happened,
произошла фамилия
let's look at someone before organized these
вот разберем кто-то до организовал эти
illegal ones,
незаконные
don't jump off, don't jump off, we
не спрыгивайте не спрыгивайте мы
'll talk about modalities, where let
поговорим про модальности где давайте
's finish with the armed
сейчас закончим с вооруженном
formation now, who organize and the
формировании кто организовывать и
armed formation, who
вооруженное формирование кто
people are the captain of the Icarus of the Germans, someone was the
люди капитан икар немцев кто-то был
leader  of course you want a lavern who has water
лидер конечно хотите лаверна кто воды
, let's see if you don’t
есть смотрите давайте так если вы не
know then it’s not the authorities with this word
знаете то не власти с этим словом что
that ukraine bombed it there, that is, it
украина что это там бомбила то есть
turns out that
получается что
you do
бомбила вы просите вы гора скачешь танка
n’t bomb it
это не законная власть но тут не можете
acted
сказать а кто каким законам действовали
here what laws they obeyed it’s not the
вот каким законам подчинялись это не
armed formations what the hell
вооруженные формирования какого хрена
can the law operate if illegality is
можна действует закон если незаконность
still under the law of which country these armed formations acted according to the
еще по закону какой страны действовали
law they now
закону они теперь
let’s at that moment
давайте вот на тот момент
but they agreed by the fact that they concluded
но они согласились тем что сделали вывод
still consider if I don’t
все еще рассмотрите если я что-то не
agree with something  for example, you already chose
соглашусь например уж у вас выбрали там
Putin there  I don’t have the right to
путина они навального я имею права
seize your
захватывать ваш город
city, look at the
нет у
fact of political disagreement with
смотрите факт политического несогласие с
something so there is no justification for a military
чем-то так не есть обоснованием военного
invasion, it’s true,
вторжения правда
turn off there, and you take faith, yes, it’s
там свернуть ну и веру вы берете да это
your right as a people,
ваше право как народа
look, yes, there is such a concept of the
смотрите да есть такое понятие права
people’s right to rebellion enshrined in
народа на восстание закрепленные
international documents
международных документов
wait again,
еще раз
we sorted it out so that the dishes the Russians
мы разобрали так что посуда русские
came to the Donbass began to kill
пришли в донбасс начали убивать
Ukrainians
украинцев
I
мне
once again gave you an example of the murdered
еще раз я вот вам назвал пример убитый
deputy of the Gorlovka council,
депутат горловского совета
this is the Donbass guy who was elected by the
это донбасский парень который и избран
Donbass people as a
был донбасс кими людьми
fascist why a fascist because it
фашист почему фашист потому что там так
was written there, that is, they simply killed  or
написано был то есть просто убили или
it says that they killed him because he
там написано что убили его за то что он
hung the Ukrainian flag back
флаг украинский по вешал назад так
instead of being taken down by militants, or well,
вместо снята боевиками или ну
let's look like this, we see the conflict
давайте вот так вот смотрите мы конфликт
from something starts further, it already goes
с чего-то начинается дальше он уже идет
to that is, it turns out that it’s not Ukraine,
до то есть получается что не украина
unless they came for the conflict
разве за конфликт
, but we  with you
пришли но мы с вами еще
again let's start like this was not their tank there
раз давайте так начнем не был их там бак
and there was no smarte sky in April were from
и не было смарте небо в апреле были от
12 Apr  ate Russian for a
12 апреля российский за
helmet somewhere the seams of a man length on April
шлема где-то швы человек длина 12 апреля
12 and 14
гласили и 14
people
человек
I don’t know what kind of people allowed to
я не знаю какие то люди разрешили там
receive weapons there what
получать оружие какие
because if you start naming
потому что если вы начнете называть
people we will further unravel who these people are and
людей мы дальше распутаем кто эти люди и
how they got these powers and how
как они получили эти полномочия и как
[music  ]
[музыка]
but it turns out, look, I gave you
но получается смотрите я вам привел
an example of how Russian militants
пример того как российские боевики после
killed Ukrainian citizens after the capture of the city,
захвата города убивали украинских
so no, well, here again, you can
граждан так нет ну вот еще раз можете
once again open about the Gorlovka
еще раз открыть про вот горловского
deputy and the student
депутата и студент
before that, if I’m a person, look, I
до этого если я человек смотрите я
say if you think that Ukraine is
говорю если вы считаете что там украина
someone there  then I killed before this disclosure, I’ll check
кого-то убила до этого раскрытия проверю
maybe I don’t know something, maybe
возможно я не знаю что то возможно от
these people are hiding something from us all over the earth, I
нас что-то скрывают эти всего земле я
now recognize you to enlighten me and now
сейчас узнаю вы меня просветить и сейчас
no one can enlighten something they shine
никто не может просветить что-то светят
shine on the lamp doesn’t enlighten
светят на не просвещает светильник
something in all not quite  regularly
что-то во всех не совсем исправно
with the current situation of
с текущее положение мусин
musin there is no such from it turns out ukraine
нету нету таких из получается украина
didn’t kill anyone and when the Russian
никого не убивала а когда российские
militants found they wanted the cities
боевики нашли захотели города начали
even vidos began to open  columns March
открываться видосы даже колонки 16 марта
16 once again defense when
вов еще раз защите когда
ukraine killed someone let's who
украина кого-то убила давайте кого
ukraine killed and when he
украина убила и когда он
tell me look tell me who
сказать мне смотрите скажите кто кого
killed whom name what day who to kill
убил назовите какого дня кого убить
people just
люди просто
in ukraine from 26 march Russian occupation began
в украине с 26 марта началась оккупация
so russian troops
российская так российские войска
shut up i want you  listen to my
помолчите я вас вы хотите послушать мой
answer or at noon dawn the troops
ответ или полудню рассвета войска
seized the parliament of the crimea the cabinet of ministers of the crimea
захватили парламент крыма кабмин крыма
so this is the officially recognized Dafa
так это официально признанный дафа
airport simferopol it is in ukraine
аэропорт симферополь это в украине
the intervention of the military began on the
началась интервенция военных на
territory of the crimea it is natural that we
территории крыма естественно что у нас
are going on again and disappeared again that we
идет еще раз и еще раз исчезла что у нас
are moving military equipment to
идет перемещение военной техники туда
where they see fit  so the border, for example,
куда считают нужным так граница например
they
то
got to the laboratory assistants who worked for
добыли к лаборанты которые работали на
Russia and prevented the movement of
россию и препятствовали перемещению
equipment, well, that they killed someone that they
техники ну что кого-то убивали что
didn’t kill anyone, the
никого не убивали
equipment itself went where it needed to,
техника себе шла туда куда нужно до
they wanted to go to the border there from Russia
захотели на границу там с россии до
until they didn’t break through, and that we
чтобы не прорывались пошли и что мы
have the right to our country  to move
имеем право своей стране перемещать
military equipment to where we see
технику военные туда куда мы считаем
fit, it also has what  e
нужным имеет также какие россии
Russia, what is the problem u went beyond the city limits
в чем проблема у поехали за черту города
again to any cities there the equipment
еще раз ни в какие города there техника
was not going to the cities the equipment was driving at a
ехала не в города техника ехала
strategic point for us to border this
стратегическим пунктом нам границы этой
further everything is clear
дальше все понятно
to give
чтобы давать
tell me before 12 right on April 12
скажите мне до 12 прямо 12 апреля
Russian terrorists invaded the
российские террористы вторглись на
territory of Donbass but this is already  with you
территорию донбасса но это уже с вами
, before April 12, someone was
определили до 12 апреля кого-то украина
killed by Ukraine there in the Donbass, tell me who
убила там на донбассе вот скажите кого
I know right now on google from liquid I know on March 13 they
я щас на google из жидкого знаю 13 марта
killed Dmitry Chernyavsky where
убили дмитрий чернявского где
[music]
[музыка]
indicates that the beating of the murders
указывает на то что избиение убийств
was only Russian
были только российского
absolutely right you paints
абсолютно верно вы красок дмитрий
Dmitry Chernyavsky killed him  Russian fighters,
чернявский его убили российские боевики
he was a member of freedom, read
это вон он был членом свободы почитайте
about Chernyavsky,
про чернявского
Dmitry Chernyavsky, so
дмитрий чернявский так
windows, he was a Ukrainian
windows он был украинец
for Ukraine, he was killed at a rally, they
за украину был его убили на митинге
cut him off, this is the very first victim if
подрезали это самая первая жертва если
we take him like that,
мы его так уже возьму
Kraslava, this is not I found it, you found it
краслава это не я нашел это вы нашли
to give porridge, I will open it for you now  let's
давать кашку я вам сейчас открою давайте
Chernyavsky on
чернявского на
[music]
[музыка]
read read about Chernyavsky
читайте читайте про чернявского
he was a member of the Freedom Party
он был членом партии свобода
on March 13  about 14 years there was a pro-Ukrainian
13 марта до 14 года был про-украинским
sale in Donetsk, as there were people who
продажу в донецке как были люди которые
agreed with something, disagreed with something, there
там чём-то согласны с чем-то не согласны
were also people who were
были также люди которые за украину так
very mass rallies for Ukraine and on March 13, 2014
очень массовые митинги и 13 марта 2014
, after the rally, he was stabbed to death by
года после митинга его зарезали
Russian militants attacked him and
российские боевики напали на него и
cut off yes
срезали да
how it happened look we are with you
как так получилось смотрите мы с вами
it’s not I remembered Chernyavsky so I
это не я вам вспомнил чернявского так я
remembered those that began after the
вспомнил же те которые начались после
official scam of the invasion of Russian
официального скам вторжения российских
militants here we look, that is, it
боевиков у тут смотрим то есть
turns out that a Ukrainian activist was
получается украинского активиста
stabbed by Russian militants on March 13
российские боевики зарезали 13 марта
after April 12 when the authors invaded
после 12 апреля когда авторы вторглись
Russian militants there  in elephants with a
российские боевики там в слоны с
throat, you further we also considered
горловкой ты дальше мы тоже рассмотрели
killed a deputy of the local council and a
убили депутата местного совета и
student elected by the people, ugli, and so
избранного народом студент угли и так
on, but you can’t name a
дальше а вы мне не можете назвать ни
single dead one before these, and it
одного погибшего так до этих да то
turns out that
получается что
Ukraine didn’t kill anyone, and Russia, as it
украина никого не убивала а россия как
came, for some reason started  to kill
пришла так почему-то начала убивать
Ukrainians from this build up in Russia
украинцы из этого нарастить в россии
a citizen of Russia Girkin came, let
пришла гражданин россии гиркин давайте
's at least
так хотя бы
Abkhazia, here we are  they yelled from Abkhazia,
абхазии вот мы говорили с абхазии
there is a fact
есть факт
an FSB worker who, even before there, two
работник фсб который еще до там два
months before that, was still a personnel officer, then
месяца до этого еще был кадровым потом
he was made like this by vacationers, but
его так сделали отпускников но
it turns out, you and I stayed on the
получается смотрите мы с вами остался на
fact that it was not Ukraine that started the truth of the
то что это не украина начала правду
war and not Ukraine, I’ll start watching
войны и не украина начну смотреть
Ukraine began to kill, they began to kill on the
украина начал убивать начали убивать
contrary  Ukrainian activists
наоборот украинских активистов так
so click there say two types I can
что там нажимаете скажите два типа могу
say that I have a job a job but then
сказать что у меня работа работа но то
let's download it if you have a
давайте уже тогда скачать если у вас
job working for us you have already gone into a dead
работа работаете у нас вы уже в глухой
corner from the
угол зашли с
discussion
дискуссии
[music]
[музыка]
wait you even tried to
ждите вы даже попробовали к этому
google it inside found yes  that another
погуглить внутри нашли да что еще одного
Ukrainian was killed, it
украинца убили
turns out look
получается смотрите
Ukrainians were killed by Russian militants
украинцев убивали российские боевики
Ukraine didn’t kill you 1 if
украина тебе того не убивал 1 если
you killed someone tell me the
кого-то убивал назовите мне назовите
dates when someone was killed I’ll check I’ll say you
даты когда кто убит я проверю я скажу вы
know you were right and so what kind of
знаете вы были правы а так вы каким
slavery you are and
рабством и
come on I love these  moments and
давай-ка я люблю эти моменты и
[music] the
[музыка]
face became a little sourer with such a
лицо кислее стало немножко с такой
daring fight
дерзкий бой
on the facts
по фактам
went that there is a
пошли что там
receptionist psychologist-and-I am a psychologist-and-I
приемная психолог-и-я психолог-и-я
am moments  when I know I drive the
я моменты когда я знаете загоняю
interlocutor, I
собеседника я
find it in order to assert myself, I
нахожу для того чтоб самоутверждаться я
will make such propaganda videos
сделаю такие пропагандистские ролики
show how the Russians are mistaken, I do
показывают как заблуждаются русски
n’t bother the game well, well, they’re
не заморачиваюсь игру ну году ну они
just poorly informed, and
просто плохо информированы и
in fact, I notice now in the
собственно ведь я замечаю сейчас в
stream of goodness and pleasure from you
потоке благости и наслаждения от вы
trying to find something, I even  doesn’t
пытаетесь что-то найти я даже не
understand that you want to find a connection
понимает что вы хотите найти связь
tip she entered particulars don’t rush
кончик у нее вошли частности не спешу
food I’ll just voice my thoughts I look at the
еду я просто озвучу свои мысли я смотрю
depth and pain in your eyes
глубину и боль ваших глазах
your eyes
ваши глаза
will be girls so development I see
будет будете девушек так развития вижу
pain in your eyes until home
боль в ваших глазах до дома
I
я
read
читаю
this find you are running somewhere  over the years,
это найти вы бегаете где-то по годам
let's go back to the fourteenth year,
давайте возвращаемся в четырнадцатый год
and yet here it is
и все таки вот он
[music]
[музыка]
Russian,
российский
let's analyze it this way, it turns out that the war
давайте так разберем то получается войну
did not start there, Ukraine is true Ukraine,
начала там не украина правда украина
we just determined that
мы что мы только что определили что
Russian militants entered from the
вошли российские боевики из
territory of Russia,
территории россии
see if militants enter from the
смотрите если и заходит боевики с
territory of Georgia dates  faith
территории грузии даты веру
[music]
[музыка]
let's stop that militants so militants further we do not speak Russian
боевики дальше мы не говорим российский
many  from the territory of Russia, correctly, the
многом с территории россии правильно
militants agreed on the territory of Russia,
боевики договорились территории россии
so under the leadership of a citizen of
так под предводительством гражданина
Russia from the tower to Girkin,
россии с башни к гиркина
he is an employee of the FSB,
он работник фсб
let's then
давайте тогда который
which four months before these events were
который четыре месяца до этих событий
still active,
еще был действующим
so let's then we stay that the
так что давайте тогда мы останемся что
militants from the territory of Russia, led
боевики с территорию россии под
by a citizen of the Russian
предводительством гражданина российской
Federation,
федерации
so
так
who was still this colonel 4 months ago,
который 4 месяца назад еще был этом
they
полковник они
entered and captured the city of Slavyansk,
вошли и захватили город славянск
we just realized that,
мы поняли только что
well, don’t turn off the zone you need
ну не отключайся зоны нужную
[music]
[музыка]
we’re leaving [music] you can grain yes yes there is real after all, it
можно грейна да да там сущая ведь
turns out that we determined
получается смотрите что мы определили
that it was not Ukraine that started the war, but
что это не украина начала войну так а
what kind of militants who came from russia,
какие то боевики которые зашли из россии
we don’t know yet, they are a Russian foreign ministry from
мы пока не знаем они российский мид из
russia, led by a citizen of the
россии под предводительством гражданина
russian federation, girkin so igor,
российской федерации гиркина так игоря
who four months before this invasion
который четыре месяца до этого вторжения
was a colonel of a company; from this,
был полковником фирмы из этого начались
hostilities began in the donbass;
боевые действия в донбассе надо нас от
we
их начала не украина это хорошо что мы
already
уже это поняли
figured it out  on Saturday, March 1, the
вот смотрите в субботу 1 марта
parties swept across Donetsk
стороны прокатились по донецку
300 euros Maidan
300 евро майдана
wounds and injuries killed more than a hundred
ранений и травм убили более сотни
people in the city in the previous
человек городским в предыдущих были
Russian flags were raised on if the beam
подняты российские флаги на если луч
first unloaded the people's governor
впервые выгрузили народного губернатора
this did
это сделал
let's it was rallies rallies no
давайте это были митинги митинги никакой
war was to give not these people then
войны не было давать не этих людей потом
send  no no no just don’t rush
отправить нет нет нет только не спешите
don’t rush wars nicknames rally you
не спешите войны ников митинге у вас в
have rallies in russia are rallies are taking place they
россии проходят митинги проходят они
find you
находят вас
wait you have in russia there is for example
подождите у вас в россии есть например
that some are for putin others against putin
что одни за путина другие против путина
there is
есть
true
правда
some but others it’s normal
одни зато другие это нормально
no one someone in odessa started there
никто кто-то в одессе начинал там
On March 1,
1 марта никто
no one looks again at what you read,
еще раз смотрите в том что вы прочитали
someone sent troops to them, did not send them
кто-то направлял войска на них не
when on March 1 we
когда 1 марта
forget it, so it turns out that
забываем это так значит получается что
from what we see, we just
из того что мы видим так мы только что
documented the hostilities with you
документально с вами разобрали
, the military began
боевые действия военные так начались
after the capture of the armed  military
после захвата вооружены военными
fighters from Russia on April 12, 2014
боевиками из россии 12 апреля 2014 года
as the basis of the meeting,
в основу совещания
okay then, let's already  I set you
ладно давайте тогда уже ставлю вас
to dedicate
посвящать
[music]
[музыка]
interrupts
прерывает
let's google here google here
давайте нагуглить вот гуглите здесь
when ukraine started specifically combat 10
когда украина начала конкретно боевые 10
not just tanks where they moved there
не просто танки куда там переезжали там
or planes cut it's normal but
или самолеты перерезали это нормально а
where and who did ukraine kill
где и кого убила украина
you just smashed me among you according to all
вы мне просто среди вас разбил по всех
arguments
аргументов
prepare to meet again prove to
подготовитесь встретимся еще докажите
me  really tell me maybe people who
мне реально скажите может люди которые
will watch a multiple of the Greeks died in his
будут смотреть кратный греков умер его
ukraine if terrorists, like in russia, they
украины если террористы как в россии они
also come terrorists 50 people are
тоже приезжают террористы 50 человек
called to ukraine,
призван украину
they don’t let planes and missiles in,
них не пускают самолеты и ракеты
you understand again, let’s do it in russia,
понимаете еще раз давайте так в россии
so you considered the Chechens terrorists so
вот вы считали чеченцев террористами так
although the state is independent, is it necessary
хотя государство независимо а нужно ли
terrorists bombed planes in general there
террористами бомбили самолеты вообще там
life was demolished formidable
жизнь была снесли грозный
I
я
participated in the second hour of the company and
участвовал второй час компании и
changed very much after 1 1
поменялось очень сильно после 1 1
company there was such a company
компании была такая компания
company
компания
[music]
[музыка]
2 1 companies very strongly if the inhabitants
2 1 компании очень сильно если жители
were opposed to everyone to
были настроены против до всех правду
cut the truth to kill because, well, such a
резать убивать потому что ну такой
setting as  actually Ukrainians on
настройку как собственно украинцев на
st  why did we come to Chechnya, but the
страх зачем мы пришли в чечню а вот
second company went to the second, and the second didn’t
вторую компанию во вторую а второе не
understand that they were deceived, and why why
поняли что их обманули а зачем зачем в
didn’t I tell Chechnya what else I
чечню не договорил еще чем я
told you, I’m a thief that then people
переговорить я вам вору что потом люди
realized that they were seized like a Ukrainian war,
поняли что хапанули как война
they would understand that they would have been deceived
украинского поймут что то бы их обманули
and the
и
author  the company, the locals are
автору компанию местные жители
actually absolutely Russian in general, but they
собственно вообще абсолютно русскими а
were only for and fought mostly
были только за а воевали в основном
mercenaries of all sorts of
наемники всяких
things
что
[music]
[музыка]
let's start with the first why russia attacked
начнем с первой почему россия напала на
chechnya in 1 company let's start attacking the floor
чечню в 1 компании начнем напала на пола
did not find troops attacked the arable land
не находила войска на пашню
and what did she do to the
напала а что она сделала
terrorists
террористам
what what
что какой
what  blockage of houses in russia up to a year
каких завал дома в россии до год
development let's
развитие давайте
see the explosions of houses began when putin came to
взрывы домов начались когда путин пришел
power began in what year in
власть начался в каком году в
volgodonsk then it was with the help
волгодонске тогда было с помощью
let's when what the [ __ ] did dudayev do let's
давайте когда какого хера сделал дудаев
talk about the
возьмите поговорим о
fact that the choice was so it turns out
том что выбор был так получается потому
because you just said that he did
что вы только что сказали что он делал
terrorist attacks  what kind of terrorist attacks are the case dudar,
теракты какие теракты дело дударь
I’m also interested in the box, too, having googled
мне же интересно ящик тоже погуглив
there and there, I’m a
туда и туда я
terrorist attack,
теракт
there’s no
нету
trouble
беда
for our brothers Chechens  which is
для братьев наших чеченцев которых
right not Kadyrov’s he is now this
правильно не кадыровцы он сейчас эту
topic,
тему разве мы
let’s evaluate the honor of Dzhokhar Dudayev when
давайте оценим честь джохара дудаева
opening
открывая
[music] the
[музыка]
explosion
взрыв
didn’t blow up several Russian residents of the
не взрывали несколько русских жителей
village
станицы
pensioner beat and robbed
пенсионер избили и ограбили у
our list then
нас списке потом
Russians
русских
let’s straighten it out there was a genocide of the
давайте так выпрямить там был геноцид
hand or there were blown up at home terrorist attacks in
руки или там взрывали дома теракты в
Russia
россии
we  understood yes you will fall out the choice God was also
мы поняли да выпадешь выбор бог тоже был
at home
дома
94 96 the
94 96 год была
first war in Chechnya was
первая война в чечне
shorter in general
короче в общем
so time will tell all people will understand in
так что время покажет все люди поймут в
good time showed that the Russians
добре время показало на что россияне
were occupiers in Chechnya before showed yes
были оккупантами в чечне до показал да
where are we now and you are now sinning and what
куда мы сейчас и вы сейчас грешить и что
there,
там
in another, they were
в другом
absolutely treated with contempt,
абсолютно такой относились с презрением
I booked, I can get what Hauser knows
бронировал могу достать что знать хаузер
earthly about Chechnya and that
земное об чечни и что
I will go in August to rest, find her,
я войду в августе отдыхать найдите ней
because I will
потому что и я там будет
get there first.
вы сначала там убивали ведь переедете
were in the
никогда не разрушить да кем вы были в
army,
армии
it doesn’t matter, it doesn’t matter,
это не важно важно не важно
machine gunner, then you were a
пулеметчик то вы были
scout, scouts over killed, yes, you
разведчик разведчики над убивали да вы
pointed some  data you were in the
наводили какие-то данные вы были в
occupational contingent this is a
оккупационном контингенте это
box for a predator the occupiers yes no they don’t
ящик для хищника оккупанты да нет не
know they don’t think
знают они так не считают
so because don’t look because you
потому что не смотрите потому что вы
put the exact
поставили там марине точную
administration there in the form of Kadyrov and he
администрацию виде кадырова так и он
just keeps the enemy still tell
просто держит все врага еще расскажите
us that we have an eternal president for
что у нас вечный президент к
everyone  if you slaughtered ours, they fought in
всех есть если вы вырезали наш воевали в
Chechnya, let’s do it like this Kadyrov fought against
чечне давайте так кадыров воевал против
and the Russians grumbled drive killed the Russians
и русских брюзжал драйва убивал русских
to kill how he was punished,
убивать как его наказали
they didn’t punish him, but it turns out there is such a
не наказали но получается есть такая
wise proverb that it can’t resist
мудро пословица не может противостоять
organizes, I understand correctly that in
организует я правильно понимаю что в
Russia you can kill Russians and you
россии можно убивать русских и тебе за
won’t get anything for it  get here an example of
это ничего не будет получать вот пример
kadyrov
кадырова
he killed Russians
он убивал русских
[music]
[музыка]
how he was punished according to the
как его наказали согласно
legislation of the russian federation
законодательства российской федерации
he fought so he fought
он воевал так он воевал
drive in google and
вбиваете в google и
shoot down
сбивать
i
я
don’t kill i
не убивайте я
fought and oxen why did you ask me
воевал и волов вы почему вы меня просили
i
я
love that you check you chickened out how
люблю что вы проверить вы струсили как
to check the game in  Beta Kadyrov looks
проверить игру в бете кадыровым выглядит
there and vodka video on
там и водки видео на
[music]
[музыка]
here is my spirin here I am writing  who
вот своей спирин вот я пишу который
fought immediately whom deputy ahmad and
воевал сразу же которым зам ахмад а
now takes the first Chechen war
теперь берет первой чеченской войны
ramzan who would participate in actions
рамзан который участвовал бы действия
against federal troops
против федеральных войск
he fought against Russians
он воевал против русских
[music]
[музыка]
participated in he participated in military
участвовал на он участвовал в боевых
operations against Russians
действиях против русских
[music]
[музыка]
the coolest Russian
самая прикольная русский
now let's see how
сейчас посмотрим как
[laughter] is
[смех]
necessary  to throw butter in oil
надо масле маслица подкинуть
so that it would be good for us
чтобы нам было хорошо
very much as you remained smart like that, you are
очень как остался умным таким типом
trying to mill there somehow,
пытаешься какими-то филировать там
and even here stupidly I don’t understand that
а даже тут тупо не понимаю что
how would I personally cook porridge for everyone,
как бы лично я варил кашу по всякому
you understand,
будет понимаешь
participated in hostilities, this is not the one
участвовал боевых действиях это не тот
who cooked porridge,
кто варил кашу
you, how are you  a military man understands
вы же ты вы как человек военный понимает
to know these I’ll tell you somehow
знать эти расскажу как-нибудь
any person who was on the
любой человек который находился на
territory,
территории
well, the hostilities, he read the
да ну боевых действий он читать
participants in the actions
участниках действий
while all the prices of the Chechen people fought
пока все цены чеченского народа воевали
against the Russian encoders weren’t so
против русским энкодеров не был такой
brave, he just grew up somewhere
смелый он просто где-то взрослую все
more and more often you hear him in the rear  cooked porridge
чаще все слышишь ты он в тылу варил кашу
cooked porridge he did not fight against the Russian
варил кашу он не воевал против русский
ball he participated in the hostilities of the
бал он участвовал в боевых действиях
by means of cooking porridge so for the
посредством варения каши так для
militants I don’t
боевиков этого не говорю
say this, for example, the
я сказал например
participant was standing in action
участник был в действие
and shooting in the forehead of a person
стоишь и стреляешь в лоб человеку
to give it how he was punished for
давать это как его покарали так за
participating in hostilities, he was according to the
участие в боевых действий он был по
law then of the Russian Federation, are these
закону тогда российской федерации это
illegal armed groups or
незаконные вооруженные формирования или
not, well, as it were
нет ну как бы есть
you don’t understand your words, yes, speak
свои слова не понимаете да говори
at
у
me duet
меня развели дуете
[music]
[музыка]
said kasheta the boy can be a
говорил кашета мальчик можно
Russian intelligence officer said that Kadyrov
российский разведчик сказал что кадыров
cooked porridge
варил кашу
this is the very topic of
это сама тема
portraits I hate these respondents love
портретах ненавижу этих респондент любят
one word but in the
одно слово а
face 0
морде 0
exact miserable people also really now
точный убогие люди тоже реально сейчас
clung will now admit I I
прицепился будет сейчас признавать я я
don’t  the fact that I’ll already have a bag, I’ll switch off,
не то что буду я уже сумку я отключимся
I’ll take the office in short, I’ll
я короче возьму-ка офисе я буду
savor it, I’ll enjoy it,
смаковать я буду наслаждаться этим
it’s just a bombshell Kadyrov
просто это просто бомбически кадыров
keychain, today I’m even
брелка я сегодня даже
honoring Ramzan Kadyrov, who in the
честь рамзана кадырова который в боевых
fighting porridge also went to this for a pair of
действиях каши тоже к этому шли за паре
myself and
себе и
I imagined I was also a participant  fighting
представлял я тоже участник боевых
on
на
this positive note, we have already been talking for an hour and
этой позитивной ноте мы уже час пусть и
finished to the word with  lova
общаемся закончил до слова слова
cooks racist
кашеварам расист
whom
которых
I think you all
я думаю вы все
[ __ ] even good deeds so we clearly once
дуже хороший делах так мы четко раз было
lost as a fact, according to chronology, the fist
терять как у фактом по хронологии кулык
studied in the Donbass, who often was so
училась на донбассе кто почасту было так
more likely to destroy packs of fingers and fingers
чаще погублю пачками пальчика а пальчики
do not google from what
не google от того чего не
alla polyanskaya is not a terrible asset, but for yours
алла полянская ужасный актив же за ваши
Dolinsk, especially in Chechnya, to
долинской особенно в чеченской
all Chechens who are brothers of the Ukrainian
всем чеченцам который братья украинского
people, not those Kadyrovites, those who are
народа не те кадыровцы те которые
real Chechens, this is a gift to you,
настоящие чеченцы это вам подарок
development of
развитие
personnel, he did not fight hostilities,
кадров он не воевал боевых действий
for example, the coloring of Kadyrov
например колорит кадыров
, Klim, subscribe to the channel,
клим оимость подписуйтесь на канал
like, write comments and on May 3, musya
ставте лайк пишите коментарии и 3 мая
descend to
опуститься до
us, really, seriously, we are my  tsetse fly
нас правде серьезно мы моему муха цеце
informative about the front glory to ukraine
информативный про фронт слава украине